Gerald R. Gill Papers MS170
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Events, 1964 -- 2006; MS170.004; 6 Linear Feet 4 full record cartons, 1 partial record carton, 1 partial oversize box
  - Tufts events, 1978 -- 2006; MS170.004.001; 1.5 Linear Feet 1 full record carton, 1 partial record carton
    - Black Alumni Weekend, name tags, 2000; MS170.004.001.011.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Black Alumni Weekend, panelist information, 2000; MS170.004.001.011.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Black Alumni Weekend, correspondence, 2000 -- 2003; MS170.004.001.011.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Events, circa 2000 -- 2005; MS170.004.001.011.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Japanese Internment Day of Remembrance, 2000; MS170.004.001.011.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Events, 2000 -- 2001; MS170.004.001.011.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Events, 2000 -- 2003; MS170.004.001.011.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Events, 2001; MS170.004.001.012.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Events, 2001 -- 2002; MS170.004.001.012.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - "4 Little Girls" movie screening, 2002; MS170.004.001.012.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Jimmy Carter documentary screening, 2002; MS170.004.001.012.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Race and ethnic studies event, 2002; MS170.004.001.012.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Events, 2002 -- 2004; MS170.004.001.012.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Events, 2003; MS170.004.001.012.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Events and clippings, 2003; MS170.004.001.012.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Japanese Internment Day of Remembrance, 2003; MS170.004.001.012.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Martin Luther King Day celebration, 2003; MS170.004.001.012.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Academic Attainments and Sporting Achievements exhibit, 2003; MS170.004.001.012.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Commencement, 2004; MS170.004.001.012.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Events, 2003 -- 2004; MS170.004.001.012.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Events, 2003 -- 2005; MS170.004.001.048.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 48, Box 2)
    - Events, 2004 -- 2005; MS170.004.001.012.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Events, 2004 -- 2007; MS170.004.001.012.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Events, 2005 -- 2006; MS170.004.001.012.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Events, 2006; MS170.004.001.012.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Another Light on the Hill exhibit, 1989 -- 2005; MS170.004.003; 1 Linear Feet 2 partial record cartons
    - Exhibit research, clippings, 1989 -- 1991; MS170.004.003.014.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Exhibit research, photocopies, circa 1999 -- 2003; MS170.004.003.014.00022; 15 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 26-40)
    - Exhibit research, notes and photocopies, circa 1999 -- 2003; MS170.004.003.014.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Exhibit research, photocopies and pamphlets, circa 1999 -- 2003; MS170.004.003.014.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Exhibit research, photocopies, 1999 -- 2003; MS170.004.003.001.00026; 2 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 26-27)
    - Exhibit planning materials, 1999 -- 2003; MS170.004.003.001.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Exhibit-related correspondence, 1990; MS170.004.003.001.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Exhibit credits, 1999; MS170.004.003.001.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Guestbook, 1999; MS170.004.003.001.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Promotional material, 2003; MS170.004.003.001.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence and promotional material, 2003; MS170.004.003.001.00032.000001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Exhibit webpage printouts, 2005; MS170.004.003.001.00032.000002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Objects, 1921 -- 2004; MS170.005; 1.8 Linear Feet 1 oversize box
  Items in this series are not arranged.
  This series contains three-dimensional objects. These include a World War II Army plaque and accompanying research for P.F.C. George R. Randolph, who was a member of the 1323rd Engineer General Service Regiment, a Black regiment. The series also includes a sign reading "Colored only, no whites," and a number of buttons and patches that are largely political in nature.
  - Buttons and patches, circa 1980 -- 2004; MS170.005.049.00001; 18 Artifact(s) (Box 49)
  - "Colored Only, No Whites" sign, 1921; MS170.005.049.00002; 1 Artifact(s) (Box 49)
    Possibly a reproduction.
  - World War II Army plaque for P. F. C. George R. Randolph HA Co. 1323rd Eng., circa 1945; MS170.005.049.00003; 1 Artifact(s) (Box 49)
  - Research for World War II Army plaque for P. F. C. George R. Randolph HA Co. 1323rd Eng., circa 2000; MS170.005.049.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 49)
- Research and subject files, 1942 -- 2007; MS170.006; 12.2 Linear Feet 9 full record cartons, 1 partial record carton, 1 partial oversize box
  This series contains a wide variety of materials collected by Gill pertaining to his research interests. The bulk of the materials consist of newspaper clippings, articles, reference copies, and notes. They cover a wide variety of topics, mostly related to African American history, Black Tufts students and alumni, sports history, and American politics. There is a large body of material on the civil rights movement in the United States, which includes a small box of index cards with information about the civil rights movement dating from 1942 to 2007.
  One particularly useful grouping of materials is the Tufts History subject files. These mostly reflect original order and provide insight into Gill's interests on campus. These materials may have been compiled as research for the "Another Light on the Hill" exhibit. There is some overlap in subject matter between this series, the Events series, and Teaching materials.
  This series is arranged alphabetically by subject. This series had very little received order. Except for the Tufts History subject files, which reflect received order, order has been imposed by the processing archivists. Labels on original folders were maintained where relevant but occurred infrequently.
  - Affirmative action, 1987 -- 1996; MS170.006.015.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Affirmative action, 1987 -- 1992; MS170.006.015.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Affirmative action, 1989; MS170.006.015.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Affirmative action, circa 1991; MS170.006.015.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Affirmative action, 1996 -- 2003; MS170.006.015.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Affirmative action, 2001 -- 2003; MS170.006.015.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Affirmative action, 2002 -- 2003; MS170.006.015.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Affirmative action, 2003; MS170.006.015.00008; 3 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 8-10)
  - African American Center at Tufts, circa 1988 -- 1995; MS170.006.015.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - African American Center at Tufts, 2001; MS170.006.015.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - African American history tours, 2000 -- 2003; MS170.006.015.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - African American student research - Rich Robinson and Greg Hunter, circa 1992 -- 2004; MS170.006.015.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - African Americans in higher education, 1984 -- 2005; MS170.006.015.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - African Americans in higher education, 1987 -- 2006; MS170.006.015.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - African Americans in higher education, 1989; MS170.006.015.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - African Americans in higher education, circa 1996 -- 1997; MS170.006.015.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - African Americans in higher education, 2000 -- 2001; MS170.006.016.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - African Americans in higher education, 2000 -- 2003; MS170.006.016.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - African Americans in higher education, 2001; MS170.006.016.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - African Meeting House in Boston, 1987 -- 2000; MS170.006.016.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - African scholarship program of American universities, circa 1960 -- 1969; MS170.006.016.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Afro-American Society, 2000 -- 2001, undated; MS170.006.016.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 6)
    Contains a copy of "Another 'Light on the Hill': History of African-American Students at Tufts, 1900-the Present."
  - American politics, 1974 -- 2000; MS170.006.016.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - American politics, 1982; MS170.006.016.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - American politics, 1991 -- 2005; MS170.006.016.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - American south, circa 1990s; MS170.006.016.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Anderson Family reunion, 1989; MS170.006.016.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Anti-fascism in Chile, 1974; MS170.006.016.00012; 2 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 12-13)
  - Anti-fascism in Chile, 1975; MS170.006.016.00013; 2 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 14-15)
  - Anti-fascism in Chile, circa 1977; MS170.006.016.00014; 2 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 16-17)
  - Arts, entertainment, and literature, 1983 -- 2001; MS170.006.016.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Arts, entertainment, and literature, 1996 -- 2005; MS170.006.016.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Arts, entertainment, and literature, 2002 -- 2003; MS170.006.048.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 48, Box 3)
  - Arts, entertainment, and literature, 2003; MS170.006.016.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Bank consult, circa 1980; MS170.006.016.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Banking, 2004 -- 2006; MS170.006.016.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Bartlett, Ruth J., circa 2000; MS170.006.016.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Bass, Charlotta Spears, 1975 -- 2004; MS170.006.016.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Black history, 1974 -- 1975; MS170.006.016.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Black history, 1980; MS170.006.016.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Black history, 1988; MS170.006.016.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Black history, 1988 -- 1989; MS170.006.016.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Black history, circa 1996 -- 1997; MS170.006.017.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Black history, circa 2000; MS170.006.017.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Black history, 2002 -- 2004; MS170.006.017.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Black history and protest in Boston, 1995 -- 2000; MS170.006.017.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Black history and protest in Boston, 1998; MS170.006.017.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Black history and protest in Boston, 2000; MS170.006.017.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Black history and protest in Boston, circa 2000 -- 2007; MS170.006.017.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Black history and protest in Boston, 2004 -- 2005; MS170.006.017.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Black-Jewish relations, 2000 -- 2001; MS170.006.017.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Black Panthers, 2003; MS170.006.017.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Blackside Inc., 1993; MS170.006.017.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Black Tufts alumni, circa 1985; MS170.006.017.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Black Tufts alumni, 1989 -- 2000; MS170.006.017.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Black Tufts alumni, 1991 -- 1996; MS170.006.017.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Black Tufts alumni, 1991 -- 1999; MS170.006.017.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Black Tufts alumni, 1996; MS170.006.017.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Black Tufts alumni, 1999; MS170.006.017.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Black Tufts alumni, 1999 -- 2001; MS170.006.017.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Black Tufts alumni, 2000; MS170.006.017.00019; 2 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 19-20)
  - Black Tufts alumni, 2001; MS170.006.017.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Black Tufts alumni, 2001 -- 2002; MS170.006.017.00021; 2 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 22-23)
  - Black Tufts alumni, 2003 -- 2005; MS170.006.017.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Black Tufts alumni, 2004; MS170.006.017.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Black Tufts faculty and staff, 1980 -- 2004; MS170.006.017.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Black Tufts faculty and staff, 2000 -- 2003; MS170.006.017.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Black Tufts students, circa 1987; MS170.006.017.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Black Tufts students, 1987 -- 1988; MS170.006.017.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Black Tufts students, 2005; MS170.006.017.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Black Tufts students, 2000; MS170.006.008.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Black Tufts students, 2001 -- 2002; MS170.006.008.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Black Tufts students, 2002; MS170.006.008.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Black Tufts students, 2004; MS170.006.008.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Blount, Stephen, 1995; MS170.006.008.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Boston area history, 1999 -- 2004; MS170.006.008.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Boston area history - League of women for community service, circa 1980 -- 2007; MS170.006.008.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Brown vs. Board of Education, 2004; MS170.006.008.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Byrd, Donald, 1992 -- 1998; MS170.006.008.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Carmichael, Stokely, 1984; MS170.006.008.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Cartoons, circa 1990 -- 2005; MS170.006.008.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Cartoons, circa 1990 -- 2005; MS170.006.008.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Chapman, Tracy, 1988 -- 1989; MS170.006.008.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Chapman, Tracy, 1989 -- 1996; MS170.006.008.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Chapman, Tracy, 1989 -- 2003; MS170.006.008.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Civil Rights Movement, 1958 -- 1964; MS170.006.008.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Civil Rights Movement, 1991; MS170.006.008.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Civil Rights Movement, 1989 -- 1995; MS170.006.008.00047; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Civil Rights Movement, circa 1990s; MS170.006.008.00048; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Civil Rights Movement, circa 2000 -- 2003; MS170.006.018.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Civil Rights Movement, circa 2000; MS170.006.018.00002; 7 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 2-8)
  - Civil Rights Movement, 2001; MS170.006.018.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Civil Rights Movement, 2003; MS170.006.018.00004; 4 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 10-13)
  - Civil War and Reconstruction, 1992; MS170.006.019.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Civil War and Reconstruction, 1995 -- 2003; MS170.006.019.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Clinton, Bill, 1993 -- 1999; MS170.006.019.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Negro Education, 1965 -- 1967; MS170.006.019.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Discrimination in healthcare, 1965 -- 1972; MS170.006.019.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Eyes on the Prize, 1986 -- 1990; MS170.006.019.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Eyes on the Prize, 1987 -- 1989; MS170.006.019.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Eyes on the Prize, 1990 -- 1998; MS170.006.019.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Farmer, James, JFK lecture, 1991; MS170.006.019.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Franklin, John Hope, 1998; MS170.006.019.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Freedom riders, 2001; MS170.006.019.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Gantt, Harvey and Lucina, circa 1963, 2003 -- 2004; MS170.006.019.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Garnett, Jessie, 1976 -- 2002; MS170.006.019.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - The Great Depression, 2002; MS170.006.019.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Harleston, Bernard, circa 1985; MS170.006.019.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Hairston, Hap, 2002 -- 2003; MS170.006.019.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Historically Black colleges and universities, 1982 -- 1983; MS170.006.019.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - History of the American South, circa 1995; MS170.006.019.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - History of the American South, circa 2000; MS170.006.019.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Howard Thurman, In Search of Common Ground proposal, 1996 -- 1997; MS170.006.019.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Howard Thurman, In Search of Common Ground proposal, 1997; MS170.006.019.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Hunt, Richard, 2005; MS170.006.019.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Immigration, 2006; MS170.006.019.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - King, Dr. Marthin Luther Jr., 2002; MS170.006.019.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Lafayette College, 1999 -- 2001; MS170.006.019.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Lafayette College, circa 1999 -- 2002; MS170.006.019.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 26)
    Contains an interview with Gerald Gill.
  - Lafayette College, 2001 -- 2002; MS170.006.019.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Lafayette College, 2002; MS170.006.019.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Lincoln, Abraham, 2002 -- 2005; MS170.006.019.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Lynchings, circa 2000; MS170.006.019.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Meanness Mania, circa 1979 -- 1985; MS170.006.020.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Meanness Mania, 1980; MS170.006.020.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, circa 1980 -- 2004; MS170.006.020.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Motley, Constance, 1994 -- 2005; MS170.006.020.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Notes of Fernando Polle, circa 1980 -- 2007; MS170.006.020.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Pacifism, 1983 -- 1993; MS170.006.020.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Pacifism, circa 1991; MS170.006.020.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Public history, oral history, the media, 2003 -- 2005; MS170.006.020.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Race at Tufts, 1980 -- 1987, 1990, 1999; MS170.006.020.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Race at Tufts, 1982 -- 1991; MS170.006.020.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Race at Tufts, 1987; MS170.006.020.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Race at Tufts, 1998 -- 2002; MS170.006.020.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Race at Tufts, 2000; MS170.006.020.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Race at Tufts, 2000 -- 2001; MS170.006.020.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Scholarships for people of color, 1988 -- 1995; MS170.006.020.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Segregation and Jim Crow, 1995; MS170.006.020.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Slavery, 1993; MS170.006.020.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Slavery, 1993 -- 1994; MS170.006.020.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Slavery, 1998 -- 1999; MS170.006.020.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Slavery, 1998 -- 2002; MS170.006.020.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Small, Roberts, 1998; MS170.006.020.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Social movement theory, 1987; MS170.006.020.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Sports and sports history, 1997 -- 2002; MS170.006.020.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Sports and sports history, 2004 -- 2005; MS170.006.020.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Sports and sports history, 1994 -- 2005; MS170.006.020.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Sports and sports history, Negro Baseball leagues, 1994 -- 2004; MS170.006.020.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Sports at Tufts, circa 1970s -- 1990s; MS170.006.048.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 48, Box 4)
  - Sports at Tufts, circa 1980s; MS170.006.048.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 48, Box 5)
  - Sports at Tufts, circa 1990 -- 2005; MS170.006.020.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Sports at Tufts, circa 1990 -- 2005; MS170.006.020.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Sports at Tufts, 2004; MS170.006.020.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Sports at Tufts, basketball, circa 1990 -- 2005; MS170.006.020.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Sports at Tufts, football, 1989 -- 1995; MS170.006.020.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Sports at Tufts, men's track, 1993 -- 1996; MS170.006.020.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Sports at Tufts, women's track, 1988 -- 1996; MS170.006.020.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Thompson, William, 1996 -- 1998; MS170.006.020.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Treating Skin of Color, 2004 -- 2005; MS170.006.020.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Tufts alumni, 1987 -- 1996; MS170.006.020.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Tufts alumni, 1998 -- 1999; MS170.006.020.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Tufts alumni, 2000 -- 2001; MS170.006.020.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Tufts alumni, 2001; MS170.006.020.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Tufts alumni, 2002; MS170.006.020.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Tufts alumni, 2005; MS170.006.020.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Tufts alumni, 2003; MS170.006.021.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Tufts alumni, 2004 -- 2005; MS170.006.021.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Tufts history, 1988 -- 1989; MS170.006.021.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Tufts history, 1988 -- 1995; MS170.006.021.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Tufts history, 1989 -- 1990; MS170.006.021.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Tufts history, 1989 -- 1990; MS170.006.021.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Tufts history, 1989 -- 2000; MS170.006.021.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Tufts history, 1990 -- 1991; MS170.006.021.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Tufts history, 1990 -- 1994; MS170.006.021.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Tufts history, 1991 -- 1992; MS170.006.021.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Tufts history, 1992 -- 1993; MS170.006.021.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Tufts history, 1993 -- 1994; MS170.006.021.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Tufts history, 1994 -- 1995; MS170.006.021.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Tufts history, 1995 -- 1996; MS170.006.021.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Tufts history, 1996 -- 1997; MS170.006.021.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Tufts history, 1998 -- 1999; MS170.006.021.00016; 2 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 16-17)
  - Tufts history, 1999 -- 2000; MS170.006.021.00017; 2 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 18-19)
  - Tufts history, circa 2001 -- 2002; MS170.006.021.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Tufts history, circa 2002 -- 2003; MS170.006.021.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Tufts history, diversity coverage, 1996 -- 1998; MS170.006.022.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Tufts history, diversity coverage, 1998 -- 1999; MS170.006.022.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Tufts history, divestment, 1985 -- 1989; MS170.006.022.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Tufts Weekly notes, circa 1980 -- 2007; MS170.006.022.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - United States history, 1999 -- 2000; MS170.006.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 50, Folder 5)
    Open for research